After sharing her tragic tale of slavery at the hands of the world nobles,
when Hancock hears of Luffy's own struggle against them,
she offers to take him to Sabaody.
Saving Ace, the next stop, the Great Prison.
You mean it? You're really going to give me a lift?
We aren't enemies anymore.
And I wouldn't lie. I'd be happy to help.
Aw, you're the best!
Well, it can be any kind of boat as long as it floats.
We will set sail tomorrow morning.
The Kuja pirates will get you safely to the Sabaody Archipelago.
With our ship?
Hope it's no trouble.
Rest well tonight, as I'm sure this visit has proved taxing.
I'll be out of here tomorrow morning.
Soon we're all going to be back together.
Goodness, we know what's on his mind.
Sonia, Mary, make arrangements for Luffy to join us as a special guest at the banquet tonight.
Are you sure?
A man attending our banquet?
Do I make myself clear?
Yes.
What kind of banquet?
It's to celebrate the Kuja pirates' safe return and to show appreciation and honor their successful haul.
So the kind with tons of food to eat, right?
Those are my favorite!
All right!
Banquet!
Are you going to come too?
No, I'm feeling a bit tired this evening.
I think I'll be going to bed early.
Oh, well, okay.
Thanks again for the ride and the food.
I can't hardly believe it!
You mean can hardly believe it.
Banquet time!
I'm surprised the steak princess has put so much trust in him.
And so quickly, too.
I think that I like you.
It's dinner time!
Bring on the food!
Banquet!
Man, you guys really got to try this stuff.
You're missing out.
Well, if you don't want it, I'll eat it.
It's hard to believe that he's the same man that saved our lives.
I hear he's leaving in the morning.
Men's bodies are as strange as the rumors said.
Did you see him stretch?
Yeah, I saw it in the arena.
They can stretch themselves quite a long way.
I'd really like to get my hands on him and have some fun.
Do you think Luffy would mind if I pulled on his face a bit?
Did you say Luffy?
Yes, that's what the man's name is.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
You watch your mouth.
It's unthinkable to address a man in such a way.
You seem to be forgetting the rules of Amazon Lily.
Fine.
Then why is Luffy at our banquet?
Huh?
Good point.
Why is a man who recently had the death sentence attending our banquet?
Ron?
Here, during our celebration.
I find it hard to believe that the snake princess suddenly forgave him.
Or maybe she didn't.
Huh?
Maybe this is a trap she laid out to trick him.
A trap?
She knows he's strong, so she can't take him lightly.
That's why she's stuffing him with food to slow him down and make him drop his guard.
Then, when he least expects it, we all attack it once and give him hell.
That's assuming a lot, but it sounds like fun.
Moving in.
Is everyone ready?
This will be his last meal.
Wait.
He's acting strangely.
No, he saw us.
You're all pissing me off!
I've had enough of this!
He must have figured it out.
We were too slow.
But it doesn't look like he'll surrender.
He'd rather fight us to the death with that pan and ladle than step down.
Just the type of thing we should expect from a man.
Move!
Let's get him!
Why isn't anyone singing?
And what's with you guys?
Now listen up!
You're not doing it right!
This is how you celebrate!
Yo-ho-ho-ho!
Gather up all of the crew!
It's time to ship out Binx's brew!
See you in blows to where?
Who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
Sing it!
Or across the ocean's tide!
Rays of sunshine far and wide!
Birds they come up here!
But they do not fly by!
Men are so weird!
Wow, this is even funnier than the dance you do when you're drunk, sweet pea!
That it is indeed.
I admit defeat.
Oh!
Oh-ho!
Oh-ho-ho-hoo!
Oh!
Oh-ho-ho!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Come on!
You can do it just like this!
Oh-ho-hoh!
Now watch!
Hellבעie!
Yeah!
You got it!
Oh...
Oh-ho!
Oh!
Yeah yeah yeah!
You got it!
Mm!
Oh!
Oh, Luffy!
You're hilarious!
– I see!
– Ooh!
– You're going to throw your nose to their mouth while holding baskets!
I'm holding baskets!
I'm shameful. Do they have no class at all?
I'm going belly talk!
Try this. It's the specialty of Maiden Island.
Pretty good. What is it?
It's pinne gorgonzola with the meat of a sea king. I really hope you like it.
I've had sea king before, but this tastes different. I like it.
Wow, it really does stretch.
It's soft and squishy like rubber.
Time's up. Step aside.
Come on, just a little longer.
No, bad enough.
This pinnade sea king meat is really good.
Is it hard to eat, though?
What the heck are you doing?! Cut it out!
I can't eat with you pulling my face around!
Sorry, we can't help it. I mean, you're leaving tomorrow, right?
There are a lot of people here who want to touch you just once.
Look!
It's taking forever! I want to touch him now!
Me too! Me too!
Get it? You're really popular!
Hi, Luffy!
I can't wait to touch you!
Dammit! You can't just start a business behind my back!
Come on, Luffy!
Please!
Tonight is the only chance we have to touch a man!
Oh, this is annoying! I can't eat with you pushing me around like this!
I want food not touching!
Wait!
Where did my break go?
Hey, where's the man?
Did he run away?
He couldn't have gotten far. Move out! Let's find him and touch him!
What the heck's the matter with them?
Keep it down.
This was all the food I could grab before I flew out of there.
It's wonderful you'll be with your friends soon. Bet you can't wait.
You said it! Anyway, I'm sorry for all the trouble I started while I was here.
I was real worried when you turned to stone.
But then you protected all of us, didn't you? Back in the arena.
I heard all about it.
You're my hero.
Thanks.
Our dear sister seems troubled.
And she's not eating.
She said she was too tired for the banquet, but she's not going to bed.
Perhaps the forced assembly of the warlords is still weighing heavily on her mind.
Tomorrow morning.
I'm out of my house tonight.
Big Sis!
Granny Mjoln!
Yes, Parker, is something wrong?
No, but the villagers wouldn't stop touching Luffy, so I brought him here.
Ah, well, it's not every day they see a man.
Hey, Granny Bean!
He's welcome to stay here until things die down.
And my name's not Bean!
It seems he has plenty to eat already.
Just bring him some tea.
Okay.
So, Granny, you like reading newspapers?
The cool news isn't delivered anywhere inside of a comm belt, so it's hard to get.
But there are certain perks when your empress is one of the seven warlords.
Even with our isolation, I like knowing what's going on in the world.
Wait a second.
Who's the warlord?
The snake, princess?
Uh, what?
She's one of the warlords, so does that mean she's actually super strong?
You're a pirate.
Surely you know who all the warlords are?
Yeah.
You think so, huh?
Ugh, don't you ever read a newspaper?
Nope.
I sure don't.
Ugh, wow.
The snake princess was crowned ruler of this country, and she was also named the captain of the Kuja Pirates around 11 years ago.
She was still young and inexperienced, but the world government put a bounty of 80 million berries on her head after just one expedition.
What did she do?
The Kuja Pirates were notorious before she became a captain.
Because of that, the world government took an interest in her right from the start, which led to their decision to invite her to become a warlord.
But now her title is about to be revoked.
Since you don't read the papers, perhaps you haven't heard.
What?
The warlords are teaming up with the Marines?
And they're going to have a war with Whitebeard and his crew?
When?
How?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on a second.
This, this is way too much for me to take in all at once.
What a foolish man you are.
You don't know anything, do you?
Now listen, that was only conjecture at this point.
I don't have any proof, but I'd say that battle is a high probability.
The world government has laid out their bait.
But Captain Whitebeard would never, ever allow his maids to be killed.
But even with that knowledge, they have announced the public execution of Port Custee Ace,
a powerful and high-ranking commander in his crew.
They have announced the public execution of Port Custee Ace, a powerful and high-ranking commander in his crew.
What's wrong?
Who?
Ace, a.k.a. Firefist Ace.
They're gonna execute...
According to this, a pirate named Blackbeard defeated Ace and gave him up to the world government.
In return, they invited him to be a warlord.
Blackbeard, huh?
This sends a strong message.
The government has caught a big fish indeed.
But more than that, if this show of authority can prove that they're stronger than Whitebeard himself, well...
Grinny!
Huh?
He's just my brother!
Port Custee Ace, the Firefist!
You're talking about my brother!
What?
My word! I never knew!
Yeah, and I didn't know anything about this!
He's gonna be killed?
But he can still escape, right?
Well, I'd say that his best chance would be if Whitebeard takes the bait and wins.
Tell me, does it say where they're gonna execute him?
In the town square of Marineford, where Navy Headquarters is located,
it says the execution will take place in one week, that's six days from today.
That's too soon!
How long will it take to get from here back to Sabaody?
Even at top speed, it would take more than a week.
A week?
But that means by the time I meet up with my crew, it'd be too late, Ace would already be dead!
Yes.
Then, how long to get to where Ace is?
Well, if he's being held at Impel Down, that would take, I would say, a week on a pirate ship.
Perhaps four days on a Navy ship.
Whoa, wait! Since when are Navy ships that fast?
There's a sea current that's reserved exclusively for the world government.
From Innie's lobby, to Impel Down, to Navy Headquarters and back.
Think of it as a giant whirlpool that connects those three facilities.
When the Gates of Justice are opened at any of these locales, usually to a Navy vessel,
then the current from the whirlpool changes and ships are ushered inside.
However, if the gates aren't opened, the ship would keep following the natural flow of the whirlpool.
Naturally, most pirate ships would rather skip this current altogether and go the long way,
though it's convenient for the Navy.
Well, what should I do then?
What do you want to do?
Don't tell me. You have your brother's veeber card?
Uh, is that the moving paper that you care so much about?
Nuh-uh. That one was a different one.
This is the card that Ace gave me.
They're also known as the paper of life,
since they give you a hint about the person's state of health,
as well as their direction.
Then, if it's that small, that means...
Back when he first gave it to me, it was ten times bigger.
Looks like Ace has been busy on his own adventure.
There's a little something I wanted you to have.
Here.
Do yourself a favor, and hang on to that.
But it's just to scrap the paper.
That paper will reunite us someday.
I'd tuck it away somewhere, for safekeeping.
You don't want it?
No, I do!
It's perfectly natural for a guy to worry
about his bungling kid brother.
Ace wouldn't be happy about his little brother saving him.
But that's still better than him dying.
Either way,
I'm gonna need to take a little side trip.
Sorry, everyone.
I have to save him.
He's the only brother I've got.
Perhaps you should think this through.
Do you have any idea how reckless this plan is?
You're facing a full-fledged war.
You'll be nothing more than a leaf whipped about by a storm,
an insect flicked away by hands far mightier than your own.
Yeah, that doesn't matter to me.
I still gotta try.
I couldn't live with myself if I let this happen.
I gotta do something.
Yes, I can see that.
So then,
you plan to rescue the most infamous prisoner in the world.
I give you a one in a million chance of success.
But in order to even try,
you need to get to the great prison where he's being held.
Once they transport him to Marinefort,
both the admirals and the warlords
will be keeping a close eye on the situation.
Keep in mind,
because your brother is the most important prisoner
in the Navy's custody,
the prison will be carefully guarded,
and it has quite the fearsome reputation,
if you haven't heard.
It may prove impossible to enter,
no matter what.
I'll worry about that when I get there.
There's no time now.
I gotta make it before they take Ace to be executed.
Give me the biggest ore you've got,
and I'll paddle like hell.
Now, hold on a second.
You'll never reach the prison by determination alone.
There is a slim chance this could work,
but...
the Snake Princess is refusing to follow the order
for the seven warlords to assemble.
But what if that changed?
If she obeyed that order?
We could take advantage of the situation
and sneak you on board their ship.
Wait, what are you...
You mean there's a Navy ship here?
Great!
Then I'm gonna go ask her if she'll do it!
Ren and Ion, it's terrible!
Inishida!
What's all the fuss about?
Thank goodness I found you quickly
when I heard I came as fast as I could.
Heard what?
It's awful!
The Snake Princess!
She's come down with the sickness,
and no one knows what it is!
She's sick!
Oh no!
Please stay strong!
Tell me, am I...
Am I going...
Going to die?
As Luffy prepares to depart Amazon Lily,
Hancock suddenly falls ill.
According to Granny Neon,
Hancock is not the first empress
to fall to this ailment,
and others have lost their lives.
What could have brought it on?
And is there a cure?
On the next One Piece!
Love is a hurricane!
Love, love, Hancock!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
God bless!